const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    question: "What is the boiling point of water",
    answers: [
      "80",
      "70",
      "0"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`100",
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the conductor from the following selections",
    answers: [
      "Cloth",
      "Paper",
      "Rubber"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Iron",
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the conductor from the following selections",
    answers: [
      "Plastic",
      "Wood",
      "Rubber"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "graphine",
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the conductor from the following selections",
    answers: [
      "paper",
      "wood",
      "Cotton"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Silver",
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the insulator from the following selections",
    answers: [
      "Silver",
      "Gold",
      "Graphine"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Plastic",
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the insulator from the following selections",
    answers: [
      "Iron",
      "Steal",
      "Gold"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cloth",
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the insulator from the following selections",
    answers: [
      "Water",
      "Copper",
      "Iron"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Wood",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is mainly made up of a conducting material",
    answers: [
      "Cooking Pot Handel",
      "Saftey Gloves",
      "Disposable Drinking Cup"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cooking Pot",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is mainly made up of non conducting material",
    answers: [
      "USB Cable",
      "Saran Wrap",
      "Light Bulb"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Fiber Optic Cable",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a Crypto Currency",
    answers: [
      "EGP",
      "USD",
      "MYR"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "DOGE",
  } 
];

module.exports = {QUESTIONS};